A Finding Aid to the Jud Fine and Barbara McCarren Papers, circa 1968-2009, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, circa 1988-2009; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 14.4 Linear feet Boxes 2-20; Oversize 21; 0.345 Gigabytes ER0001-ER0005
  - Los Altos Center Public Art Project, Archival Resource Key
    - Research Material, Native American History, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Research Material, Puvunga History, circa 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Footings A., circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Inverted Wood Column L-1, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Menhir L-3, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Faux Menhir L-4, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Midden L-5 A (Sewer well) B (Fountain Upright), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Sound Mound L-6, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Newt L-7, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Stone Pavers L-8, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Los Angeles 3rd Street Tunnel, Archival Resource Key
    - Budget, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, Sketches, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Presentation, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles Metro, Blue Line Ave. 57 Station, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1993-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
    - Competition for Pedestrian Bridge, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Contract, circa 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - Contract, Project Description, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Conservation Report, circa 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Cross Walk Designs, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Column Design, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Bid, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Engineering Details, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Inverted Post #1, circa 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Inverted Post #2, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Preliminary Drawings, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Fabrication, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Stone Tree, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Stone Tree Bids, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Footings, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Lights, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Design Meeting, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Meetings, circa 200-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Notes, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Plans, Original Drawings, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Box 4)
    - Plans and Drawings, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Press, 2000, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Photographic Material, circa 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Research Material, Tiles, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Los Angeles Metro, Orange Line, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Budget, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Design Concept, circa 2004-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Project Overview, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
    - Contract, circa 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Tatsumi Associates (Landscape Architect), circa 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Meeting Notes, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Public Meetings, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Insurance, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Invoices, circa 2003-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Punch Lists, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Rotator Sign 1, circa 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Rotator Sign 2, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Plants, circa 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Materials, circa 2003-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records; see ER0002. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Photographic Material, Digital Photographs, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.049 Gigabytes Three computer files (Folder ER0002)
    - Research Material, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Research Material, Rotator, circa 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Landscape Plans and Drawings, circa 2002-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Box 18)
  - Los Angeles Zoo, Habitat Proposal, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - MAIZ, César Chávez Park, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Artist Assessment Report (Dec. 1996), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Contracted Artwork, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Proposed Master plan (RJM Design), 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - RJM Design Group Bid, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - RJM Design Group, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - RJM Design Group, Contract and Invoice, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Contract, Project Background, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Drawings, Source Images, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Plans and Drawings (Frogs, Fish, Corn, Loteria), circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Source Material, Loteria/ Tarot Cards, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Map, Plan Drawings, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Fabrication, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Workshop (Mar. 9 1996), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Meeting Minutes, First District Park Advisory (Aug. 26 1996), Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Meeting Notes, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Notes, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Bench Panels, Fireform Porcelain, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Icons, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Fish, Corn, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Frogs, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Frog Wall, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Press, circa 1996, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
    - Research Material, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Research Material, Source Images, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32-33)
    - Research Material, César E. Chávez, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Research Material, Long Beach History, circa 1981-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Research Material, USC Library Materials, 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Research Material, Thesis by Keith Miller on César Chávez Park, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Manhattan Beach Streetscape, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence (P&D Consultants), circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Proposal, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Drawings and Design, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, P&D Consultant, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Drawings, Reduced and Enlarged, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Drawings, Research Material, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Research Material, Primary Sources, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Research Material, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Modesto 10th Street Plaza, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, 1998-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Contract, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Contract, Cold Spring Granite Co., circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Budget, Construction, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Architect, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Stone Masters, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Artist Visits, Proposals, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Artwork Water, Wealth, Contentment, Health, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Drawings, Diagrams, Sketches, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Flag Pole, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Fountain Plans, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Installation Schedule, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Installation Session 1 (Jan.-Sep. 1999), circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Installation Session 2 (Sep. 1999-Apr. 2000), circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Installation Session 3 (Apr. 2000-), circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Installation Session 3 Oversize (May 2000-), Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Invoices, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Insurance, Legal, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Travel, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Presentations, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Notes, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Photographic Material, Snapshot Albums (Construction, Fabrication, Installation), circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29-31)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Research Material, Jud Fine Family History in Modesto, circa 1950s, 1978, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Research Material, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Montebello Corporate Yard Expansion, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Budget, circa 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Maps, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Santa Barbara Greenhouses, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Invoices, circa 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Opening, Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Notes, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Research Material, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Central Library, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Research Material, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - North Hollywood Streetscape Design, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ogawa Plaza Oakland, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Contract, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Text for Steps, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
    - Steps, Notes, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Notes, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Photographic Materials, circa 1992-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Research Material, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Pacific Enterprises Commission "Circuit" Interstate World Center, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Palisades Cultural Affairs Department, Rec. Center, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Budget, Project Description, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Kanner Architects, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Jerseys, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Frames, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Plaque Text, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Invoices, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Notes, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Press Clippings, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Photpgraphic Material, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Research Material, Trophies, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Research Material, Balls, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Research Material, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Pasadena City College, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, Notes, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Notes, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Grounds Plan, Research Material, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Research Material, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Pershing Square, Archival Resource Key
    - Contract, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Contract Amendment, Artwork Commission, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Budget, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Art Plan, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Art Plan, Presentation and Handouts, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Cultural Affairs Commission, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Consolidated Terrazzo, Subcontractor, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Mike Gilbert, Subcontractor, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Langdon-Wilson (Architecture and Planning), circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Legoretta Arquitectos, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Maguire Thomas Partners, circa 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Olin Ltd., circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Project Background, circa 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Property Owner Association, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Project Directory, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Monuments, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Artist Selection Panel, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Scope of Artist Work, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Other Artists, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Fabrication, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Paving, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Bench Text, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Presentation, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, Fountain, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Plans, Reduction, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Research Material, Postcards, circa 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Research Material, Telescopes, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Research Material, Monuments and Architectural Details, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Research Material, Watts Towers Fountains, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Research Material, Writings on Pershing Square, circa 1980-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Research Material, circa 1980s-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - PlanetTrek, Archival Resource Key
    - Proposal, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Budget, Art Concept, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Artist Biographies, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Notes, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Research Material, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - San Antonio Mission Trail, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Contract, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - Budget, Construction, circa 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Final Plan, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Public Art, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Travel, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Notes, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
    - Printed Material, Miscellaneous, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Press Clippings, circa 1997-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Photographic Material, Snapshot Albums, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Photographic Material, Slides, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Research Material, Lowriders, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Research Material, San Antonio History, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - San Fair Pocket Park, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, Contract, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Contract, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Project Background, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Bids, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Construction, circa 2001-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Map, Drawings, Layout, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Text Translations, circa 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - San Jose, King Road Golfcourse, Foretokens, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Project Plan and Drawings, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Quick Crete, Subcontractor, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Plaque, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Pedestal Podium, circa 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Locations, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Construction Document, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Notes, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Photographic Material, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Research Material, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - San Jose, Tech Museum of Innovation, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Presentation, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco Zoo, Archival Resource Key
    - Contracts, circa 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
    - Budget, 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Proposal Draft, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Bids, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Architect Agreement, 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Marin Monument Text, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco Arts Commission, 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Charisma Design Studio, Inc., circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Cold Spring Granite, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Finnegan Construction, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Robert La Rocca & Associates, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - CSG Field Dimensions, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Meeting (Apr. 11, 2000), circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Permissions, Final, circa 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Fabrication Bid, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Travel, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - License Agreement (Zooetta Stone), circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Drawings, circa 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Insurance, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Invoices to SF Arts Commission, circa 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Invoices, circa 2000-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Final Payment, circa 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Receipts, circa 1998-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Granite Sand Blasting, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Reopening Event (June 26, 2002), circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Pangea Medallion, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Zooetta, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Element 1, Frogs, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Element 2, Zooetta Stone, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Element 3, View Tube, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Element 6, Ship Panels, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Element 9, Wall Cladding, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Element 10, Passageway Paving, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Notes, circa 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Photographic Materials, circa 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Research Material, Frogs, Ships, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Research Material, Gebhard Style Glossary, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Santa Barbara Bowl, Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Research Material, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13-15)
  - Santa Clara Valley Transportation Authority (SCVTA), Archival Resource Key
    - Correspondence, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Contract, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Subcontracting Agreement, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)